PROJECT MANAGER

JEACQUELINE RÍOS MARTÍNEZ

CONTACT

- jeacqueline.rios@outlook.com
- 81-2006-5988 / 55-1966-4038
- Monterrey, N.L.
- 🦰 Jeacqueline

SUMMARY

Project Manager with experience in project management, efficient in time management with team oriented management style and assertive communication and newly acquired knowledge in GitHub, Javascript, HTML, CSS and Node.js, Fast selflearner and highly creative as well an insatiable as intellectual curiosity.

Certified in Scrum, Design Thinking and Python.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate

Italian: Basic

JavaScript 1

Python



WORK EXPERIENCE

5T S.A. de C.V.- Scrum Master

January 2020 - December 2020

- Creation of KPI's for projects.
- Create daily meetings with the team.
- Monitoring the project to verify the alignment with the scope, time and costs.
- Identification of risks, roadblocks and issues to properly escalate, contain/resolve and follow-up.

NYCE Laboratorios, S.C.- (Social Service)

June 2018 - December 2018

- Standard monitoring with the norm NMX-EC-17025.
- Food and textile sampling.
- Determine product alignment with the stablished quality standards (Net weight, total cocoa butter).
- Preparation of solutions with required specifications.
- Handling of laboratory equipment.

EDUCATION

2022- Full Stack Flex Boot Camp . (In progress) Tec de Monterrey. EdX Boot Camps

2018- Masters degree in Project Management.

2020 UNITEC

2014- Bachelor degree in Science - Chemical Engineering.

2018 UNITEC

CERTIFICATES

- IBM | Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner.
- IBM | Enterprise Design Thinking Co-creator.
- IBM | Enterprise Design Thinking-Team Essentials for Al.
- SCRUMstudy | Scrum Fundamentals Certified.
- Certiprof | Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate.
- Mimo | Python.
- edX | Introduction to Data Science and Big Data.

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

- Assertive communication.
- Leadership.
- Team work.
- Time management.
- Project management.
- Fast learning ability.
- Proactive.
- Creative.
- Logic and critical thinking.

- MS Office (Word, Teams, Excel. Outlook,etc).
- Methodology PMI.
- Power Bl.
- Python.
- MS Project, Visio MS.
- Confluece.
- Jira.
- Monday.
- Jama.
- Monday.
- GitHub.
 - Javascript.
- HTML & CSS.

BOOTCAMP

COMING SOON THIS KNOWLEDGE



EDUCATION

Full Stack Flex Boot Camp . (In progress)
November 2022- May 2023 Tec de Monterrey. EdX Boot Camps

- GitHub
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript 🕗
- Node.js
- Express.js 🕗
- MySQL

• Heroku



- React.js
- Java
- MERN Stack
- Database Theory
- MongoDB